http://www.hparch.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
This website (www.hpa.ltd) belongs to Harrison & Pitt Architects Ltd of 29, Castle Hill, Lancaster, Lancashire, LA1 1YN. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.
The information we collect about you
We collect information about you when you complete a contact form on this website. We only collect the following personal data about you:
Your name
Company name
Telephone number
Email address
Website usage information is also collected using cookies. Our cookies policy provides more information about our use of cookies.
How we use this information about you
Website contact form completions
This information is used to process and respond to your enquiry. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee this service to you.
All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in the UK; however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the European Union. No third parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so.
Website usage information
Website usage information is used to measure, monitor and improve the performance of our website and marketing campaigns. Please see our cookies policy for further information.
How long do we keep this information?
Completed contact form enquiries will be retained for a maximum of seven years after which time they will be destroyed. However, should you become a client, our client terms and conditions will take over, details of which will be provided at the time.
Access to your information and correction
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information please contact: The Office Manager, Harrison & Pitt Architects Ltd, 29, Castle Hill, Lancaster, LA1 1YN
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. In the case of access and correction requests, please provide as much detail as you can about the particular information you need, in order to help us locate it.
Our use of cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.
Our cookies policy provides more information about our use of cookies.
You can set your browser not to accept cookies – there are guides at www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org about how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.
Third party data processors
We use a number of third party data processors who are carefully chosen and comply with relevant Data Protection legislation. These third party processors and their relevant privacy policies are here:
Google, based in the USA – collecting / reporting website usage information. Google Privacy Policy.
Microsoft (Bing), based in the USA – collecting / reporting website usage information. Microsoft Privacy Policy.
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their privacy policies.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
The Office Manager
E-mail: 01524 32479
Telephone: hpa@hparch.co.uk
Post: Harrison & Pitt Architects Ltd, 29, Castle Hill, Lancaster, LA1 1YN
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will provide any updates on this web page.
This privacy policy was last updated on 15th May 2018.
Have you got a project you want to discuss?
Contact us
Latest News
10 Things You Never Knew An Architect Did
Architects are highly trained professionals who design the built environment around us. However, an Architect’s role involves much more than […]
Read more
Working Hard on Leisure Projects
It may have been a strange year for some, with furlough and lockdown keeping many people away from work, but […]
Read more
HPA – Planning for the Future
HPA Chartered Architects are delighted to announce a new appointment to strengthen our expert planning team. Claire Walters has joined […]
Read more
The Value of an Architect
When choosing someone to help you design your next project, you have a number of options. Traditionally Architects are the […]
Read more
10 Things You Never Knew An Architect Did...
04/11/2020
Architects are highly trained professionals who design the built environment around us. However, an Architect’s role involves much more than […]
Read more
Working Hard on Leisure Projects...
23/09/2020
It may have been a strange year for some, with furlough and lockdown keeping many people away from work, but […]
Read more
HPA – Planning for the Future...
17/09/2020
HPA Chartered Architects are delighted to announce a new appointment to strengthen our expert planning team. Claire Walters has joined […]
Read more
The Value of an Architect...
29/07/2020
When choosing someone to help you design your next project, you have a number of options. Traditionally Architects are the […]
Read more
View Archive
hpa@hpa.ltd
HPA Chartered Architects,
29 Castle Hill, Lancaster,
Lancashire, LA1 1YN
Services
Architecture and design
Planning advice and consultancy
Sustainable building design
Sectors
Leisure and Hotels
Industrial and Commercial
hpa@hpa.ltd
HPA Chartered Architects,
29 Castle Hill, Lancaster,
Lancashire, LA1 1YN
HPA Ltd 2014. All rights reserved. Registered in England no: 4391977
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkRead more
